let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the output of the following Python code snippet?  print(3 * 'Hello' + 'World')",
    answer: "HelloHelloHelloWorld",
    options: [
      "HelloWorld",
      
      "HelloHelloHello",
      "HelloHelloHelloWorld",
      "Syntax Error"
      
      
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
question: "What will be the value of x after executing the following Python code?"+"  "+"x = 5"+" " +"x+= 2"+" "
     +"x *= 3",
    answer: "21",
    options: [
      "15",
      "10",
      "11",
      "21"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " Which of the following statements is used to define a function in Python?",
    answer: "define myFunction():",
    options: [
      "function myFunction():",
      "define myFunction():",
      
      "def myFunction()",
      "myFunction():"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the output of the following Python code?"+" "+"my_list = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5]"+"   "+"print(my_list[1:3])",

    
    answer: "[2, 3]",
    options: [
        "[2, 3]" ,
       "[1, 2, 3]" ,
       "[3, 4]" ,  
      "[2, 3, 4]" 
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following data types is mutable in Python?",
    answer: "list",
    options: [
      "int",
      "float",
      "list",
      "tuple"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb:6,
    question:" What does the range() function in Python return?",
    
    answer:"A generator object",
    options:[
        "A list of integers",
        "A tuple of integers",
        "A generator object",
        "An iterator"
        
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:7,
    question:"What is the output of the following code?" +"  "+"x = [1, 2, 3]"+"  "+"y = x"+" "+"y.append(4)"+"  "+"print(x)",
    
    answer:" [1, 2, 3, 4]",
    options:[
        " [1, 2, 3]",
        " [1, 2, 3, 4, 4]",
        " [1, 2, 3, 4]",
        " [1, 2, 3, 4, 3]"
        
        
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:8,
    question:"What does the pass statement do in Python?",
    answer:"Does nothing",
    options:[
        "Terminates the program execution",
        "Skips the current iteration in a loop",
        "Does nothing",
        "Raises an exception"
        
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:9,
    question:" Which of the following is the correct way to open a file named 'data.txt'for writing in Python?",
    answer:'file = open("data.txt", "w")',
    options:[
        'file = open("data.txt", "w")',
        'file = open("data.txt", "r")',
       'file = open("data.txt", "a")',
       'file = open("data.txt", "wb")'
        
        
        
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:10,
    question:"What is the output of the following code?"+"   "+'print("Python"[::-1])',
    
    answer:"nohtyP",
    options:[
        "nohtyP",
        "Python",
        "pyt",
        "P"
        
        
    ]
  },
  
];